I got one!
What is that?
I shall grant you a wish.
Three of a kind.
Sorry, but it looks like I take this hand.
Lady Luck's a pal of mine, ya know.
Well, I guess I'll be taking these...
A full house!
Sorry, but Lady Luck's my best friend!
Well, I guess I'll be taking these...
You're pretty good, aren't you?
Okay, fine, I'll play another hand with you.
Come on, no more cards.
More importantly, you now owe
me ten ice cream cones, you know.
I want you to buy them now!
You'll make yourself sick if you eat
all ten at once. Make it one a month.
What are you talking about?!
You don't even have enough
money to buy ice cream cones?!
Um... Is this is Devil May Cry, the place
that "gets the job done whatever it may be"?
Yeah, that's right. But that only
applies when I'm in the mood.
And today I'm in a lousy mood... So get lost.
What are you saying?!
You better buck up, get to work
and earn some ice cream money!
Welcome! Please come in!
I'll make you some tea!
I see... So you want me to
rescue your older brother,
who was arrested on false charges, correct?
Yes.
What's the charge?
It's murder...
But there's no way my older brother
would have done something like that!
To begin with, the man who died,
Claude, was my brother's best friend!
I wonder...
Sometimes the better the
friends, the deeper the hatred...
That's not true! My brother
is the last person who would--
You have any proof?
--I...
--Go home.
It's like the stupid mother saying,
"My child would never do that!"
There's nothing less
trustworthy than feelings like that.
To begin with, do you even
have money? I don't come cheap.
Ten ice cream cones should
about cover things...
I'll give you this as payment.
It's pretty!
No thanks. I only work for cash.
What's she think she's doing?
Well, I guess we've accepted her payment...
Hey! Anyone here?
Yep.
One strawberry sundae.
We don't have treats for the kiddies here.
I didn't think you would... I can
never get 'em at places like this.
But man, business is slow, huh?
Yeah...
I just haven't had any
customers since that incident.
What a nuisance...
Tell me everything you
know about that incident.
Who are you? A detective?
It doesn't matter either way.
You tell me that story,
and I'll tell you a secret
that'll have customers lined up out the door.
I still can't believe it.
Kerry and Claude were best friends...
Well, it seems Kerry was
on a losing streak...
All of a sudden I heard
this really loud scream.
It's my...
It's my fault...
"It's my fault."
That's what this "Kerry" guy said?
Yeah. That was taken as a
confession and he was arrested.
There were no other
customers here, after all.
And Claude's whole body
was just melted away...
You'd have thought it was
the work of the devil.
So where is this Kerry guy now?
I hear he's locked up at Devil's Prison.
--Morrison?
--I heard.
You're not actually thinking about
going to Devil's Prison, are you?
What if I am?
Here's some friendly advice.
Just forget about it.
There's a rumor that no one's ever
gone in there and come out alive.
It's supposedly worse than hell.
I doubt even you could make it out of there.
Wanna bet?
Why the hell would I do that?
It's not like I'd get any
money from you even if I won.
Hey! How about that secret that'll
have customers lined up out the door?
Just put strawberry sundaes on the menu.
--Are you serious?
--Then that bastard...
You bastard!
What d'you think you're doing?!
Just taking out the trash.
Gotta keep the town clean, ya know.
Don't you dare mess with us!
This is a really nice place you got here...
A person could probably take a good
nap here, and not be bugged by anyone.
It'll be a long nap all right.
You'll probably get to
nap for the rest of your life.
You know a guy named
Kerry Márquez? He's a pal of mine.
That guy's in a special cell block
for committers of heinous crimes.
A special cell, eh?
They must serve great food there, I bet...
You'll just be in a normal
cell for having committed
property damage and
infliction of personal injury.
Don't worry, though.
No matter what kind of cell you're in,
Devil's Prison is Devil's Prison.
You must be a real bad apple
if you're carrying all this stuff.
Oh, those are just accessories.
I just made a little
mistake in regards to their size.
Well, don't you look cute and talk cute...
And this firm body of
yours looks so delicious...
You be a good boy and do like I tell
you, and I won't do anything mean to you.
You're the one who looks delicious...
Being all marbled with fat and all...
A special cell!
Throw him in a high security cell!
Hey.
There should be some guy in here
by the name of "Kerry Márquez."
You know him?
Who are you?
Kerry...
I'm here 'cause someone out
there believes you're innocent.
It's useless. Both of us will be killed soon.
Oh?
Well, why don't you just
give me the real story
so I have something to think
about on my way to the other side.
I've told this story so many
times, but no one will believe me!
Who can blame them?!
Like anyone's gonna believe
that a devil was responsible...
A devil?
Yeah... I didn't even believe it.
That something like that was even possible...
I shall grant you a wish.
What is the problem? I said I will
grant you a wish. Tell me what you want.
You don't have a wish?
Any wish will do. This
is a rare chance for you.
Y-You'll... really... grant my wish?
Yes. Tell me now.
Okay, give me money! I want to
be the richest man in the world!
No way.
Okay, give me power! I want to be
the most powerful man in the world!
No. It wouldn't benefit you.
Okay, I want women! I want all
the women in the world to be mine!
No. I'm not interested.
Heh, I guess there are some pretty
smart-ass devils out there, huh?
So? In the end, what was
the wish he granted you?
Yeah... Well, he certainly granted my wish...
I wished for...
Sorry, looks like I win again.
Let's play one more!
Hey, give it a rest. I got
to be getting to work soon.
Sure, just up and run after your win!
Drop dead, you jerk!
I shall grant your wish.
Huh?
Your wish has been granted.
No! Wh-What the hell have I...
What's going on?
What happened to him?!
It's my... It's my fault...
I killed him... I...
Of course I wasn't
serious when I told him to die!
But that bastard... he killed my friend!
I understand what you're saying,
and I believe your story.
The only thing left to do
is get out of this place.
Well, I wonder how we'll do that...
I'm telling you, it's impossible!
This place is worse than hell!
It's started again!
Attention all prisoners.
It's time for a little game of tag.
If you don't want to die, I suggest you run!
Run! Run!
What's this all about?
It's a game of tag! But it's not just a
game. If they catch you, they kill you!
The guards hunt us like game!
I told you I'd make you my little bitch...
Huh. So devils have taken possession
of you guys' twisted desires.
Huh... What pretty jewels.
I bet they'd be perfect
for decorating my room.
I shall grant you a wish.
Well, you're definitely
not your typical devil.
What is the problem? Tell me what you want.
Okay, I might as well give it a shot.
I'll take eternal youth, so I
can remain flawlessly beautiful.
No way.
How about all the jewels in the world? I'd
like to try bathing in a tub filled with them.
No. I'm not interested.
Well, can I at least have
a nice dress or something?
No. It wouldn't benefit you.
You're useless. Die, then!
Listen up. You guys are criminals.
"Tag"? You got to be kidding me.
I just reported this to police headquarters.
Wh-What?!
This time judgment will be passed on you.
And don't even think about trying to run away.
I mean, this place is famous for
being an inescapable hell, isn't it?
Idiot!
We run this place! We know how to get out!
All right, open the gate!
My thanks.
Yep, nothing like the air on the outside.
Y-You bastard!
I'll raise.
So you escaped from Devil's
Prison, huh? Impressive as always.
I guess... I'll raise, too.
So what happened? Call.
It's a long story.
Full house.
Sorry about that.
Yeah, I'm sorry too... Royal straight flush.
Aren't you holding one too many cards?
Yeah, I threw in an extra as a bonus.
Knock it off! You know you just got busted!
You can die, for all I care.
I shall grant your wish.
It's him! He's the one who...
Ah, what a good boy.
I'm surprised you'd come to
me and save me the trouble.
Lady, who is this dude?
Search me. Some generous
mask that'll grant you any wish.
St-Stop!
I'm sorry.
Please stop!
No way.
I'm begging you! Spare me!
No. Not interested.
Do it Dante! Kill him!
What's wrong? Will you spare me or not?
The next line is "It wouldn't
benefit you," you know that.
I'll take this!
Wouldn't expect anything less of you, Dante.
You really are strong...
I can't help but respect you.
You... What kind of scheme
are you cooking up?
Well, you'll find out sometime.
One should always save the fun part for last.
Just you watch, Dante...
So, what are you going to do now?
Nobody's going to call you a liar anymore.
You've been cleared of all suspicion.
Thank you so much for
everything you've done for me.
But, maybe the world would
be better off if I were in prison.
What do you mean by that?
Do you still feel responsible
for your friend's death?
It's not just that...
My younger sister's dead because of me too.
Younger sister?
Yeah. Lynn's always been frail.
But when I got arrested, she was stricken
with worry and her condition went downhill.
She must resent me.
Does this sister of yours
have sapphire-colored pigtails?
Yeah.
Your younger sister doesn't resent you.
That ring...
I bought that for Lynn...
How did you come by it?
The person who hired me paid with
this in the place of money, saying:
"Please save my older brother."
How can... that be...?
See ya.
I got you! Today I want
my ten ice cream cones!
Just one.
No way.
Well, how about another game of poker?
No. I'm not interested.
Everyone has a past.
The problem is that people's pasts
are not always picture-perfect.
When you decide to
confront your detestable past,
what determines whether you'll
be able to dispel its darkness
is how fruitful the time you've
spent since then has been.
In other words, I shouldn't
have anything to worry about.